addicted2decorating.com 2019-05-15

# Privacy Policy - Addicted 2 Decorating®

Addicted 2 Decorating, a property of Kristi Linauer, LLC, is committed to keeping any and all personal information collected of those individuals that visit our website and make use of our on-line services accurate, confidential, and secure. Our privacy policy has been designed and created to ensure those affiliated with Addicted 2 Decorating of our commitment and realization of our obligation not only to meet but to exceed most existing privacy standards.

This Privacy Policy Agreement shall apply to Addicted 2 Decorating and shall govern any and all data collection and usage thereof. Your use of Addicted 2 Decorating implies consent to the following data procedures expressed in this agreement.

**Collection of Information**

This website collects various types of information, such as:

  * Voluntarily provided information which may include your name, email address, etc., which may be used when you sign up for services you have requested.
  * Information automatically collected when visiting our website, which may include cookies, third party tracking technologies and server logs.

Addicted 2 Decorating will only collect personal information that you knowingly and willingly provide by way of surveys, newsletter sign up forms, comment forms, and other similar voluntarily-submitted information. It is the intent of this site to use personal information only for the purpose for which it was requested.

Addicted 2 Decorating may also have the occasion to collect anonymous demographic information that may not be unique to you and may even gather additional or other personal and/or non-personal information, such as age, gender, household income, political affiliation, race and religion, at a later time.

It is even possible that we may gather information about your computer hardware and/or software. Such collected information may include, but may not be limited to, your IP address, browser type, domain name, access time and various website addresses. The gathering of this information may be used for maintaining the quality of service we provide, as well as providing overall general statistics related to the use of our website and others.

**Use of Information Collected**

Addicted 2 Decorating may collect and may make use of personal information to assist in the operation of our website and to ensure delivery of the services you need and request.

Addicted 2 Decorating does not now, nor will it in the future, sell, rent or lease any of its customer lists and/or names to any third parties.

Addicted 2 Decorating may find it beneficial to share specific data with their trusted partners in an effort to conduct statistical analysis. Those third parties shall be strictly prohibited from making use of your personal information, other than to deliver those services which you requested, and as such they are thus required in accordance with this agreement to maintain the confidentiality of all your information.

Addicted 2 Decorating may disclose your personal information, without prior notice to you, only if required to do so pursuant to applicable laws and/or in a good faith belief that such action is deemed necessary or required to:

  1. Conform to decrees, laws and/or statutes or in an effort to comply with any process which may be served upon Addicted 2 Decorating;
  2. Safeguard and/or preserve all the rights and/or property of Addicted 2 Decorating; and
  3. Perform under demanding conditions in an effort to safeguard the personal safety of users of Addicted 2 Decorating and/or the general public.

**Children Under Age of 16**

Addicted 2 Decorating does not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under the age of sixteen (16) without verifiable parental consent. If it is determined that such information has been inadvertently collected on anyone under the age of sixteen (16), we will immediately take the necessary steps to ensure that such information is deleted from our system’s database. Anyone under the age of sixteen (16) must seek and obtain parent or guardian permission to use this website.

**Unsubscribe or Opt-Out**

All users and/or visitors to our website have the option to discontinue receiving communication from us and/or reserve the right to discontinue receiving communications by way of email or newsletters. To discontinue or unsubscribe to our website please use the “unsubscribe” link located at the bottom of the newsletter, or send an email that you wish to unsubscribe to the email on our website. If you wish to unsubscribe or opt-out from any third party websites, you must go to that specific website to unsubscribe and/or opt-out.

**Links to Other Web Sites**

Our website does contain links to affiliate and other websites. Addicted 2 Decorating does not claim nor accept responsibility for any privacy policies, practices and/or procedures of other such websites. Therefore, we encourage all users and visitors to be aware when they leave our website and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy Agreement applies only to the information collected by this website, Addicted 2 Decorating.

**Security**

Addicted 2 Decorating will endeavor and will take every precaution to maintain adequate physical, procedural and technical security with respect to its offices and information storage so as to prevent any loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure or modification of the user’s personal information under our control.

**Changes to Privacy Policy Agreement**

Addicted 2 Decorating reserves the right to update and/or change the terms of our privacy policy, and as such we will post those change to our website homepage at [www.addicted2decorating.com](https://www.addicted2decorating.com/), so that our users and/or visitors are always aware of the type of information we collect, how it will be used, and under what circumstances, if any, we may disclose such information. If at any point in time Addicted 2 Decorating decides to make use of any personally identifiable information on file, in a manner vastly different from that which was stated when this information was initially collected, the user or users shall be promptly notified by email. Users at that time shall have the option as to whether or not to permit the use of their information in this separate manner.

**Acceptance of Terms**

Through the use of this website, you are hereby accepting the terms and conditions stipulated within the aforementioned Privacy Policy Agreement. If you are not in agreement with our terms and conditions, then you should refrain from further use of our site. In addition, your continued use of our website following the posting of any updates or changes to our terms and conditions shall mean that you are in agreement and acceptance of such changes.

**How to Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding the Privacy Policy Agreement related to our website, please feel free to contact us at the following email.

addicted2decorating@live.com
